Growing up，I was always afraid of the dark
从小到大 我一直害怕黑
Now I'm about to confront my deepest fears
现在我即将面对我最深的恐惧
in a place where no light can reach
进入阳光找不到的地方
The ocean is mysterious and vast
海洋神秘而辽阔
I sense fear and loneliness
让我感觉到恐惧和孤独
when i dive into the deep waters
当我潜入深海之中
Will i feel isolated or free
我会感到孤立，还是自由
Rock climbing is a challenge
攀岩是一项挑战
Both mental and physical
无论是精神上还是身体上
Can i make it to the top
我能登上顶峰吗
is part of the adventure
这是冒险的一部分
Where i reach my limit？
我会在何处抵达自身极限？
I'm excited to find out
我很期待能找到答案
This time I've come to yangshuo for rock climbing
这次我来到阳朔攀岩
It involves many movements
攀岩包含许多专业动作
And i want to learn how to climb in a safe manner
我想学习规范、安全的攀岩技巧
What will it be like on my own
孤身前行会是怎样一番体验
Will i be able to navigate my way
我能否找准前行的方向
and embrace the solo journey？
坦然接纳这场独自奔赴的旅程？
I am in Badain Jaran desert
我身处巴丹吉林沙漠
inner Mongolia
内蒙古境内
I have never been to a desert before
我从前从未踏足沙漠
The vast emptiness here amazes me
这片无边旷野，令我心生震撼